Margaret Henderson Floyd Architectural Slide Collection MS175
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Architectural slides, 1955 -- 1998; 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001; 16.0 Linear Feet
  - US architects, 1960 -- 1997; MS175.001.005
    - Meigs/Old Pension Building, 1970; MS175.001.012.00012 (Box 12)
      Meigs, Montgomery Cunningham
    - Mills, Robert, 1970 -- 1973; MS175.001.012.00013 (Box 12)
      Mills, Robert
    - Mullet, A. B., 1973; MS175.001.012.00014 (Box 12)
      Mullett, Alfred Bult
    - Munday, Richard, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.012.00015 (Box 12)
      Munday, Richard
    - Newton, Dudley/BelAir Estate, 1968; MS175.001.012.00016 (Box 12)
      Dudley, Newton
    - Notman, John/Philadelphia Athenaeum [1], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.012.00017 (Box 12)
      Notman, John
    - Notman, John/Union League Club [2], 1970; MS175.001.012.00018 (Box 12)
    - Parris, Alexander/Faneuil Hall Market/City Hall Quincy, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.012.00019 (Box 12)
      Parris, Alexander
    - Parker, Minerva [1], 1976; MS175.001.012.00020 (Box 12)
      Nichols, Minerva Parker
    - Parker, Minerva [2], 1976; MS175.001.012.00021 (Box 12)
    - Platt, Charles/New Concoran Gallery, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.012.00022 (Box 12)
      Platt, Charles
    - Pope, John Russell/The Waves, 1994; MS175.001.012.00023 (Box 12)
      Pope, John Russell
    - Post, G.B., 1982; MS175.001.012.00024 (Box 12)
      Post, George Browne
    - Potter, E.T./Mark Twain House [1], 1972 -- 1976; MS175.001.012.00025 (Box 12)
      Potter, Edward Tuckerman
    - Potter, E.T./Mark Twain House [2], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.012.00026 (Box 12)
    - Potter, E.T./Church of the Good Shepard/Colt Memorial [3], 1977 -- 1978; MS175.001.012.00027 (Box 12)
    - Potter, W.A./Pittsfield Athenaeum, 1976 -- 1978; MS175.001.012.00028 (Box 12)
      Potter, William A
    - Preston, W.G./Vendome Hotel/Chadwick Leadworks [1], 1983; MS175.001.012.00029 (Box 12)
      Preston, William Gibbons
    - Preston, W.G./Savannah Cotton Exchange [2], 1979 -- 1982; MS175.001.012.00030 (Box 12)
    - Price, Bruce, 1994; MS175.001.012.00031 (Box 12)
      Price, Bruce
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.013.00001 (Box 14)
    - Ransome Concrete Co. #1 United Shoes Co. #1, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00002 (Box 13)
    - Ransome Concrete Co. #2 United Shoe Co. #2, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00003 (Box 13)
    - J. Renwick/ Corcoran Gallery Washington/ Smithsonian Inst. Washington, 1973 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00004 (Box 13)
      Renwick, James
    - J. Renwick #2/ Springfield Museum/ George Walter Smith Museum, 1973 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00005 (Box 13)
    - Shaw and Hunnewell/ Back Bay Houses, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00006 (Box 13)
      Shaw and Hunnewell
    - Shaw and Hunnewell #2 Hill Hurst/ The Pines/ Wellesley, MA, 1972 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00007 (Box 13)
    - Shaw and Hunnewell #3 Wellesley Town Hall/ Bacon Library, Natick, 1965 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00008 (Box 13)
    - Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson, and Abbott, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00009 (Box 13)
      Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson & Abbott
    - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, 1971; MS175.001.013.00010 (Box 13)
      Skidmore, Owings & Merrill
    - Smithmeyer & Peltz, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00011 (Box 13)
      Smithmeyer & Pelz
    - Snell and Gregerson Unity Close/The Cushing House, 1972 -- 1977; MS175.001.013.00012 (Box 13)
      Snell and Gregerson (Boston, Mass.)
    - R.C. Sturgis JMS Grave/ Am. Antiquarian Society Worcester/Rockwood Manchester, 1968 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00013 (Box 13)
      Sturgis, R. Clipston (Richard Clipston), 1860-1951
    - R.C. Sturgis Cambridge Fire Station, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00014 (Box 13)
    - S.J.F. Thayer/ City Hall in Providence, 1973; MS175.001.013.00015 (Box 13)
      Thayer, Samuel J.F.
    - Wm. Thorton/ Octagon House/ Homewood, Baltimore MD, 1970 -- 1973; MS175.001.013.00016 (Box 13)
      Thorton, William
    - Town, Ithiel/First Unitarian Worcester, 1975 -- 1976; MS175.001.013.00017 (Box 13)
    - Trost & Trost Occidental Life Building, 1985; MS175.001.013.00018 (Box 13)
      Trost & Trost
    - Upjohn, Richard/ Grace Church Providence, R.I./ St. Stephen's Providence, R.I., 1973 -- 1976; MS175.001.013.00019 (Box 13)
      Upjohn, Richard, 1802-1878
    - Upjohn, R #2 St. Paul's Church, Brookline/St. Luke's Clermout, NY/ Grace Church Manchester NH/ Kingscote Newport/ Ed. King House Newport, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.013.00020 (Box 13)
    - Upjohn Jr., R./ State Capitol Hartford, Conn, 1974; MS175.001.013.00021 (Box 13)
    - Inventory, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.014.00001 (Box 14)
    - Vaughn, Henry, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.014.00002 (Box 14)
      Vaughan, Henry
    - Vaux, Calvert, 1969 -- 1976; MS175.001.014.00003 (Box 14)
      Vaux, Calvert
    - Ware/VanBrunt [01], 1971 -- 1977; MS175.001.014.00004 (Box 14)
      Ware, William Robert; Van Brunt, Henry
    - Ware/VanBrunt [02], 1965 -- 1975; MS175.001.014.00005 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [03], MS175.001.014.00006 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [04], 1975; MS175.001.014.00007 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [05], 1972 -- 1975; MS175.001.014.00008 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [06], 1974 -- 1975; MS175.001.014.00009 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [07], 1972; MS175.001.014.00010 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [08], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.014.00011 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [09], 1972 -- 1978; MS175.001.014.00012 (Box 14)
    - Ware/VanBrunt [10], 1976; MS175.001.014.00013 (Box 14)
    - Warren/Bucklin, 1973; MS175.001.014.00014 (Box 14)
      Warren, Russell; Bucklin, James W.
    - Wells, Joseph, 1972 -- 1978; MS175.001.014.00015 (Box 14)
      Wells, Joseph
    - Wheelock, 1971; MS175.001.014.00016 (Box 14)
      Wheelock, Merrill G.
    - Wheelright, E.M., 1993; MS175.001.014.00017 (Box 14)
      Wheelwright, Edmund March
    - Wight, P.B., 1971; MS175.001.014.00018 (Box 14)
      Wight, Peter Bonnett
    - Wills, R.B., 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.014.00019 (Box 14)
      Wills, Royal Barry
    - Rancho Palos Verdes, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.014.00020 (Box 14)
    - Young, A.B., 1972 -- 1973; MS175.001.014.00021 (Box 14)
      Young, Ammi B. (Ammi Burnham)
  - Brigham, Charles (MA, NH, NY), 1968 -- 1997; MS175.001.006
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.015.00001 (Box 15)
    - Ch. Brigham Belmont/ Church, Jamaica Plain 1859, Chas. Bughem, 1972 -- 1978; MS175.001.015.00002 (Box 15)
      Brigham, Charles, 1841-1925
    - C. Brigham Boston #1/ A. Burrage Hse 314 Comm. 1899, 1970; MS175.001.015.00003 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Boston #13/ Christian Science Church (Ext) 1906, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.015.00004 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Boston #4/ Christian Science Church (interior), 1976 -- 1997; MS175.001.015.00005 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Boston #2/ Boston State House 1889-1903, 1970 -- 1977; MS175.001.015.00006 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Fairhaven #3/ Unitarian Church #1, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.015.00007 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Fairhaven #4/ Unitarian Church #2/ 1914 Rogers Tomb/ Parish House, 1969 -- 1997; MS175.001.015.00008 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Fairhaven #1/ Rogers School 1885/ Town Hall 1890-1894, 1969 -- 1970; MS175.001.015.00009 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Fairhaven #2/ Millicent Library Fairhaven 1891-1893/ Stable of Roger's Estate/ High School 1904, 1970; MS175.001.015.00010 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham/ Foxboro State Hospital/ Watertown/ Ch. Brigham House, 1968 -- 1976; MS175.001.015.00011 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Laconia, N.H./ Library 1903 Laconia, N.H., 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.015.00012 (Box 15)
    - C. Brigham Morris, N.Y./ Bellewood Mt. Morris, N.Y. 1886, 1974 -- 1997; MS175.001.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Hunt, Richard Morris (NC, CT, IL, NY, PA, RI), 1965 -- 1997; MS175.001.007
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.016.00001 (Box 16)
    - Asheville, NC R.M. Hunt/ Biltmore/ R.M. Hunt, 1965 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00002 (Box 16)
    - New Haven, CT RM Hunt/Scroll and Key Yale University/ Divinity School Yale, 1972 -- 1976; MS175.001.016.00003 (Box 16)
    - Chicago, IL, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00004 (Box 16)
    - Genesco, NY Bear Monument, 1974 -- 1975; MS175.001.016.00005 (Box 16)
    - Hyde Park, NY, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00006 (Box 16)
    - New York, NY RM Hunt, 1972 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00007 (Box 16)
    - Milford, PA, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00008 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI RM Hunt/ TG Appleton House Busk House/ Belcourt/ Oliver HP Belmont House, 1972 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00009 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI The Breakers, 1974 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00010 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI RM Hunt/ Chateau-sur-mer, 1969 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00011 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI RM Hunt/ Chateau-sur-mer #2, 1972 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00012 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00013 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI RM Hunt/ Griswold House, 1969 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00014 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI/ Griswold House, 1994; MS175.001.016.00015 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI RM Hunt/ Hypotenuse/ Indian Spring/ Marble House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00016 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI/ Marquand House/ Ochre Court, 1972 -- 1974; MS175.001.016.00017 (Box 16)
    - Newport, RI Charles Shields House/ Swiss Chalet/ Travers Block, 1969 -- 1997; MS175.001.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Longfellow, Alden & Harlow, 1966 -- 1997; MS175.001.008
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.017.00001 (Box 17)
    - LAH Aids, 1974 -- 1983; MS175.001.017.00002 (Box 17)
      Longfellow, Alexander Wadsworth, 1854-1934
    - BERR [Boston Elevated Rail Road] - Design, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.017.00003 (Box 17)
    - LAH Mass - Boston, 1987; MS175.001.017.00004 (Box 17)
    - LAH Mass - Boston Readville, 1993; MS175.001.017.00005 (Box 17)
    - LAH Mass - Cambridge, 1966 -- 1990; MS175.001.017.00006 (Box 17)
    - LAH Mass - Cambridge, 1976; MS175.001.017.00007 (Box 17)
    - LAH (1897) Phillip Brooks House / Harvard University, Cambridge, 1987 -- 1994; MS175.001.017.00008 (Box 17)
    - [Harvard University - Carey Athletic Building], 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.017.00009 (Box 17)
    - LAH Mass- Hingham/ Gov. John Andrew House / LAH Mass- Lancaster / Lancaster Town Hall, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.017.00010 (Box 17)
    - Jamaica Plain, MA / LAH (1891) Arnold Arboretum, 1994; MS175.001.017.00011 (Box 17)
    - LAH Maine- Deer Isle / J.G. Croswell House, 1987 -- 1988; MS175.001.017.00012 (Box 17)
    - LAH Maine- Northeast Harbor / Hopkinson Cottage, 1990; MS175.001.017.00013 (Box 17)
    - LAH NY- Albany / Wemple House, 1988; MS175.001.017.00014 (Box 17)
    - Wentworth-Coolidge House / New Hampshire, Portsmouth, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.017.00015 (Box 17)
    - Inventory, MS175.001.018.00001 (Box 18)
    - Slides from Clayton 1 / LAH Clayton / H. J. Heinz / Mrs. B. F. Jones / Charles Lockhart / R. B. Mellon, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.018.00002 (Box 18)
      Longfellow, Alexander Wadsworth, 1854-1934; Alden, Frank Ellis; Harlow, Alfred Branch
    - Slides from Clayton 2 / LAH Rowenlea (A. R. Peacock), 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.018.00003 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Edgeworth / LAH PA-Cresson / McCague / W.H. Singer Hs., 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.018.00004 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Homestead / Homestead Library, 1988; MS175.001.018.00005 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-McKeesport / LAH PA-Osterling, 1988; MS175.001.018.00006 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Pittsburgh / 1897-1907 Carnegie Institute 1 / Science Wing E.L. Barnes, 1987; MS175.001.018.00007 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Pittsburgh / 1897-1907 Carnegie Institute 2, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.018.00008 (Box 18)
    - Carnegie Institute 4 / Workers, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.018.00010 (Box 18)
    - Carnegie Institute 5 / Procession of the People / Carnegie Institute (1892), 1969; MS175.001.018.00011 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Pittsburgh / Churches Braddock Meth-Episc Ch. / Ascension Church / MacClure Ave. Presbyterian Ch. / West End Methodist Ch., 1987 -- 1988; MS175.001.018.00012 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Pittsburgh / Homes 1 / Alden Hs #1 / Hornetts, Allegheny / McClelland Hs E End, 1987 -- 1988; MS175.001.018.00013 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Pittsburgh / Homes 2 / Neimann-Billings Hs / Pontefract Hs, Allegheny, 1983 -- 1987; MS175.001.018.00014 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Pittsburgh / Libraries and Conservatory, 1987 -- 1988; MS175.001.018.00015 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Sewickley 1, 1987 -- 1988; MS175.001.018.00016 (Box 18)
    - LAH PA-Sewickley 2 / LAH PA-Vandergrift, 1988; MS175.001.018.00017 (Box 18)
    - LAH WV-Lazearville / Vancroft 1, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.018.00018 (Box 18)
    - LAH WV-Lazearville 2 / Vancroft 2, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.018.00019 (Box 18)
    - LAH WV-Lazearville 3 / Vancroft 3 - Out buildings, 1988; MS175.001.018.00020 (Box 18)
    - [Vancroft], 1988; MS175.001.018.00021 (Box 18)
    - [Vancroft], 1988; MS175.001.018.00022 (Box 18)
    - [Vancroft], 1988; MS175.001.018.00023 (Box 18)
    - [Vancroft], 1988; MS175.001.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Nash, Joseph, 1970 -- 1998; MS175.001.009
    - Inventory, 1998; MS175.001.019.00001 (Box 19)
    - Nash #1, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.019.00002 (Box 19)
      Nash, Joseph, 1809-1878
    - Nash #2, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.019.00003 (Box 19)
    - Nash #3, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.019.00004 (Box 19)
    - Nash #4, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.019.00005 (Box 19)
    - Nash #5, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.019.00006 (Box 19)
    - Nash #6, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.019.00007 (Box 19)
    - Nash #7, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Peabody & Stearns (IL, MA, RI), 1965 -- 1997; MS175.001.010
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
    - [Robert Peabody portrait], 1988; MS175.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
      Peabody, Robert Swain, 1845-1917; Peabody & Stearns (Boston, Mass.)
    - Beverly, 1972; MS175.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
      Peabody, Robert Swain, 1845-1917; Stearns, John Goddard, 1843-1917; Peabody & Stearns (Boston, Mass.)
    - Peabody + Stearns #2 [Boston, MA / Brookline, MA], 1973 -- 1993; MS175.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
    - [Peabody + Stearns / N. Beverly, MA / Boston, MA], 1983 -- 1988; MS175.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
    - Peabody + Stearns (C2 3/91), 1990 -- 1991; MS175.001.020.00006 (Box 20)
    - Peabody + Stearns / City Hall, Worcester, 1973 -- 1993; MS175.001.020.00007 (Box 20)
    - Peabody + Stearns #3 / Bailey House Newton, MA / Matthews Hall, Harvard College, 1965 -- 1975; MS175.001.020.00008 (Box 20)
    - Peabody + Stearns #4 / Old Parish House, 1979; MS175.001.020.00009 (Box 20)
    - Peabody + Stearns #5 / Mass State Bldg - World's Columbian Exhibition, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.020.00010 (Box 20)
    - Peabody + Stearns [Newport, RI], 1974 -- 1976; MS175.001.020.00011 (Box 20)
    - Peabody + Stearns [Newport, RI], 1994; MS175.001.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Richardson, Henry Hobson (CT, DC, IL, MA, NY, PA, RI), 1965 -- 1997; MS175.001.011
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. Boston/ Brattle Square Church/ Crown Shield House/ Oliver Ames House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00002 (Box 21)
      Richardson, H.H. (Henry Hobson), 1838-1886
    - H.H.R. Boston/ Trinity Church/ Trinity Rectory, 1965 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. Cambridge, MA, 1971; MS175.001.021.00004 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. Cambridge/ Austin Hall/ Sever Hall Harvard, 1972 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. Dedham, MA, 1971; MS175.001.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. Malden, MA/ Converse Library, 1972; MS175.001.021.00007 (Box 21)
    - (1881) Marion, MA/ HH Richardson Percy Browne House, 1994; MS175.001.021.00008 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. Newton, MA/ Baptist Church/ Bigelow, 1966 -- 1994; MS175.001.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. No. Easton, MA/ Library/ Ames Memorial, 1972; MS175.001.021.00010 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. No. Easton, MA/ The RR Station, 1972 -- 1974; MS175.001.021.00011 (Box 21)
    - H.H.R. No. Easton, MA/ The Gate Lodge, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00012 (Box 21)
    - Palmer, MA/ HH Richardson B and A RR Station Palmer, MA (1881-5), 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00013 (Box 21)
    - Gurney House HHR Pride's Crossing, MA, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00014 (Box 21)
    - HHR Quincy, MA/ Crane Library, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00015 (Box 21)
    - Springfield, MA/ (1871-74) HH Richardson Hampden Co. Courthouse Springfield, MA, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00016 (Box 21)
    - HHR Wellesley Hills, MA, 1967; MS175.001.021.00017 (Box 21)
    - HHR Woburn, MA, 1966; MS175.001.021.00018 (Box 21)
    - HHR New London, CT/ Union Station, 1967; MS175.001.021.00019 (Box 21)
    - HHR Chicago, Ill./ Glessner House/ Marshall Field Store, 1971 -- 1974; MS175.001.021.00020 (Box 21)
    - HHR Albany, NY, 1974 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00021 (Box 21)
    - HHR Buffalo, NY/ Dorsheimer House/ State Hospital, 1973 -- 1974; MS175.001.021.00022 (Box 21)
    - HHR Pittsburgh, PA, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00023 (Box 21)
    - HH Richardson Allegheny Co. Jail Pgh PA 1893-1896, 1974 -- 1994; MS175.001.021.00024 (Box 21)
    - HH Richardson Allegheny Co. Jail Pgh PA 1893-1896, 1994; MS175.001.021.00025 (Box 21)
    - HH Richardson Supt. Hse Allehgeny Co. Jail Pgh 1893-1896, 1994; MS175.001.021.00026 (Box 21)
    - Newport, RI HH Richardson 1874 WM Watts Sherman Hse, 1969 -- 1994; MS175.001.021.00027 (Box 21)
    - HHR Washington, D.C., 1974 -- 1997; MS175.001.021.00028 (Box 21)
    - [HH Richardson], 1975; MS175.001.021.00029 (Box 21)
      Sherman (Wyo.); Richardson, H.H. (Henry Hobson), 1838-1886
    - [HH Richardson], 1974; MS175.001.021.00030 (Box 21)
    - Hartwell & Richardson/ S. Kelley House, 1972; MS175.001.021.00031 (Box 21)
  - Sturgis, John Hubbard, 1960 -- 1997; MS175.001.012
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.022.00001 (Box 22)
    - J.H. Stugis Brookline/ JL Gardner "Green Hill" Wahen St. (1884-5), 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00002 (Box 22)
      Sturgis, J.H. (John Hubbard), 1834-1888
    - S&B Brookline/ Hyscop House/ Hubbard College Brookline, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00003 (Box 22)
    - S&B Cambridge/ Hooper House/ Carey House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00004 (Box 22)
    - S&B Dedham, MA/ Stephen Werd House, 1990; MS175.001.022.00005 (Box 22)
    - S&B Dedham/ Codman Hse/ Dedham R.R., 1972 -- 1974; MS175.001.022.00006 (Box 22)
    - A. Lawrence House Groten #1, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00007 (Box 22)
    - [Sturgis & Brigham], 1987; MS175.001.022.00008 (Box 22)
      Sturgis & Brigham
    - S&B Jamaica Plain/ Pine Bank, 1968 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00009 (Box 22)
    - S&B Lancaster/ John Thayer Hse, 1971; MS175.001.022.00010 (Box 22)
    - S&B Lincoln/ The Grange, 1972 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00011 (Box 22)
    - S&B Manchester/ Sunny Waters, 1968 -- 1972; MS175.001.022.00012 (Box 22)
    - S&B Nahant/ S&B Pride's Crossing/ H.P. Kidder House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00013 (Box 22)
    - S&B Stoughton/ Railroad Station, 1972; MS175.001.022.00014 (Box 22)
    - S&B Wellesey/ Hunnewell Cottage 1, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00015 (Box 22)
    - JH Sturgis Hunnewell Cottage Wellesley, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.022.00016 (Box 22)
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.023.00001 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00002 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 1/ Chas. Codman 57 Marlborough/ Edw. Codman 53 Marlborough, 1970 -- 1983; MS175.001.023.00003 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 2/ Hollis Hunnewell 315 Dartmouth/ Frances Hunnewell 278 Clarendon, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00004 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston/ Museum of Fine Arts, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00005 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 3A/ Museum of Fine Arts, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00006 (Box 23)
    - Deacon House Panels-MFA, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00007 (Box 23)
    - JH Sturgis 3B/ Museum of Fine Arts 1870-6/ J.H. Sturgis "Art School"/ Walter Smith "Art Education", 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00008 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 4/ H.L. Higginson 8-10 Fairfield, 1970 -- 1983; MS175.001.023.00009 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 5/ Church of the Advent, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00010 (Box 23)
    - Sturgis and Brigham Eccles. Boston (5A), 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00011 (Box 23)
    - Sturgis and Brigham E. Rollins Morse House 167 Comm Ave (5B), 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00012 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 6/ Mrs. J. Gardner 152 Beacon, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00013 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 6A/ John L Gardner 152 Beacon St, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00014 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 7/ Richard Codman House 17 Brimmer St/ Dexter 55 Beacon St, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00015 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 8/ Mass. Hosp. Life 50 State St./ AME's Store Morrison Ave., 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00016 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 9/ F.L. Ames #1 306 Dartmouth, 1970 -- 1983; MS175.001.023.00017 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 10/ F.L. Ames #2 306 Dartmouth, 1970 -- 1975; MS175.001.023.00018 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 11/ F.L. Ames #3 306 Dartmouth, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.023.00019 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 12/ Nathaniel Thayer 239 Commonwealth/ E.V.R. Thayer House 17 Gloucester St, 1970 -- 1983; MS175.001.023.00020 (Box 23)
    - J.H. Sturgis Boston 13/ H.A. Whitney House 261 Beacon, 1970; MS175.001.023.00021 (Box 23)
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
    - J.H. Sturgis Independence, MO/ Trinity Church, 1970; MS175.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
    - J.H. Sturgis Portsmouth, RI/ Barstow House, 1969 -- 1997; MS175.001.024.00003 (Box 24)
    - J.H. Sturgis Newport, RI/ Francis Bacon House/ Theo Davis House, 1968 -- 1997; MS175.001.024.00004 (Box 24)
    - Cushing House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.024.00005 (Box 24)
    - Frederick Rhinelander House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.024.00006 (Box 24)
    - Sturgis & Brigham Concord, New Hampshire, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.024.00007 (Box 24)
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.025.00001 (Box 25)
    - Barrytown, NY/Franklin Delano House [1], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.025.00002 (Box 25)
      Sturgis, John Hubbard
    - Barrytown, NY/Franklin Delano House [2], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.025.00003 (Box 25)
    - Barrytown, NY/Franklin Delano House [3], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.025.00004 (Box 25)
    - Barrytown, NY/Franklin Delano House [4], 1972; MS175.001.025.00005 (Box 25)
    - Barrytown, NY/J.H. Sturgis/Franklin Delano House [5], 1972; MS175.001.025.00006 (Box 25)
    - Barrytown, NY/Sturgis Interior Hall/Franklin Delano House [6], 1972; MS175.001.025.00007 (Box 25)
    - Barrytown, NY/Frank Wills Work/Franklin Delano House, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.025.00008 (Box 25)
    - Geneseo, NY/J.H. Sturgis/The Homestead [2], 1975 -- 1976; MS175.001.025.00009 (Box 25)
    - Geneseo, NY/J.H. Sturgis/The Homestead [1], 1975 -- 1976; MS175.001.025.00010 (Box 25)
    - Geneseo, NY/J.H. Sturgis/General James Wadsworth/Livingston Wadsworth, 1974; MS175.001.025.00011 (Box 25)
    - Geneseo, NY/J.H. Sturgis/Windows in St. Michael, 1975; MS175.001.025.00012 (Box 25)
    - Sturgis and Brigham Steamhouse/Walter Langdon (Vanderbilt) Estate, 1994; MS175.001.025.00013 (Box 25)
      Sturgis, John Hubbard; Brigham, Charles
    - Walter Langdon Estate, Hyde Park, NY/Sturgis and Brigham Gardeners Cottage, 1994; MS175.001.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd (AZ, IL, PA), 1971 -- 1996; MS175.001.013
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
    - Wright, F.L./Robie House [1], 1971; MS175.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
      Wright, Frank Lloyd
    - Wright, F. L./Unity Temple/Nathan Moore House [2], 1971; MS175.001.026.00003 (Box 26)
    - Wright, F.L./Scottsdale/Tucson [3], 1978; MS175.001.026.00004 (Box 26)
    - Wright, F.L./Bear Run, P.A. [4], 1988; MS175.001.026.00005 (Box 26)
    - Wright, F.L./Bear Run, P.A. [5], 1988; MS175.001.026.00006 (Box 26)
    - Wright, F.L./Bear Run, P.A., 1988; MS175.001.026.00007 (Box 26)
    - Wright, F.L./Bear Run, P.A./Falling Water, 1988; MS175.001.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - English geography, 1960 -- 1997; MS175.001.014
    - Inventory, 1997; MS175.001.027.00001 (Box 27)
    - Abbotsbury, 1971; MS175.001.027.00002 (Box 27)